Register of the Daniel Lerner collection
Hoover Institution Archives
- Intelligence Reports, 1944-1948 (Boxes 28-50)
  - United States.
    - Office of Military Government for Germany
      - Greater Hesse
        - Information Control Division
          - Information Control Weekly Summary, Memorandum regarding,., November 1946 (Folder 47: 4)
          - Reports on various subjects (Folder 47: 5)
      - Information Control Division
        - Daily Intelligence Digest
          - ., 1945
            - ., September (Folder 47: 6)
            - ., October (Folder 47: 7)
            - ., November (Folder 47: 8)
            - ., December (Folder 47: 9)
          - ., 1946
            - ., January (Folder 47: 10)
            - ., February (Folder 47: 11)
            - ., March (Folder 47: 12)
        - Opinion Surveys,., October 1947 (Box-folder 48: 1)
      - Office of the Director of Intelligence
        - Intelligence Bulletin,., January 1946 (Folder 48: 2)
        - Spotlight,., December 1945 (Folder 48: 3)
      - Office of the Director - Weekly Field Report,., October 1945 (Folder 48: 4)
      - Public Relations Office - For Information of Correspondents,., April-July 1947 (Folder 48: 5)
      - Württemberg-Baden
        - Information Control Division - Reports on various subjects,., 1946-1947 (Folder 48: 6)
        - Ochsenfurt - Weekly Report,., October 1946 (Folder 48: 7)
    - Office of Strategic Services
      - General (Folder 48: 8)
      - European Political Report
        - ., 1944 (Folder 48: 9)
        - ., 1945 (Folder 48: 10)
      - Field Intelligence Study,., 1945
        - ., June-July (Folder 48: 11)
        - ., August-September (Folder 48: 12)
        - ., October
          - ., 8-21 (Folder 48: 13)
          - ., 24 (Box-folder 49: 1-2)
        - ., November-December (Folder 49: 3)
      - Paris Intelligence Weekly,., 1944-1945 (Folder 49: 4)
      - Weekly French Intelligence Report,., September-December 1944 (Folder 49: 5)
      - Weekly German Intelligence Summary,., November 1944 (Folder 49: 6)
    - Office of Strategic Services. London
      - List of reports from Germany,., 1944-1945 (Folder 49: 7)
      - Reports from various countries,., 1944-1945 (Folder 49: 8)
    - Office of Strategic Services. Paris - Reports from various European countries,., 1944-1945 (Box-folder 50: 1-2)
    - Office of War Information
      - Basic Central Directive, Memoranda regarding,., September 1945 (Folder 50: 3)
      - Semi-Monthly Report,., November 1944 (Folder 50: 4)
      - Weekly Propaganda Directive,., April-May 1945 (Folder 50: 5)
    - War Department - Reports regarding airplanes,., 1918-1919 (Folder 50: 6)
- Interrogation Reports, 1944-1945 (Boxes 51-66)
  Records of interrogations of German POWs, civilians, and foreign workers; questionnaires; studies. Arranged alphabetically by issuing agency
  - General
    - Undated
      - General (Folder 51: 1-2)
      - Displaced persons.
        See INTERROGATION REPORTS/General/Undated/German civilians and foreign workers
      - German civilians and foreign workers (Folder 51: 3)
      - War criminals, Suggested subjects in interrogation of (Folder 51: 4)
    - ., 1944
      - ., August (Folder 51: 5)
      - ., September
        - General (Folder 51: 6-8)
        - General (Box-folder 52: 1)
        - Questionnaires (Folder 52: 2-3)
      - ., October (Folder 52: 4-7)
      - ., October (Box-folder 53: 1-2)
      - ., November (Folder 53: 3-7)
      - ., November (Box-folder 54: 1-2)
      - ., December (Folder 54: 3-9)
    - ., 1945 (Box 55)
      - ., January (Folder 55: 1-7)
      - ., January (Box-folder 56: 1)
      - ., February (Folder 56: 2-11)
      - ., February (Box-folder 57: 1-2)
      - ., March (Folder 57: 3-6)
      - ., March (Box-folder 58: 1-4)
      - ., April (Folder 58: 5-7)
      - ., April (Box-folder 59: 1)
      - ., May (Folder 59: 2-3)
      - ., June (Folder 59: 4)
      - ., July (Folder 59: 5)
      - ., August (Folder 59: 6)
      - ., September (Folder 59: 7)
      - ., October (Folder 59: 8-10)
      - ., November (Folder 59: 4)
  - Allied Expeditionary Forces. Supreme Headquarters. (Box 60)
  - Supreme Headquarters Allied Expeditionary Forces. Psychological Warfare Division
    - General
      - Undated
        - General (Folder 60: 1)
        - Displaced persons.
          See INTERROGATION REPORTS/Supreme Headquarters Allied Expeditionary Forces/Psychological Warfare Division/General/Undated/ Foreign workers
        - Foreign workers (Folder 60: 2)
      - ., 1944
        - ., August (Folder 60: 3)
        - ., September (Folder 60: 4)
        - ., October (Folder 60: 5)
        - ., November (Folder 60: 6)
        - ., December (Folder 60: 7)
      - ., 1945
        - ., January (Folder 60: 8)
        - ., February (Folder 60: 9)
        - ., March (Folder 60: 10)
        - ., April (Folder 60: 11)
        - ., June (Folder 60: 12)
        - ., July (Folder 60: 13)
    - German press (Folder 60: 14)
    - Standard Form POW Interrogation #2,., 1944 (Box 61)
      - ., August (Folder 61: 1)
      - ., September (Folder 61: 2-5)
      - ., October (Folder 61: 6-9)
      - ., October (Box-folder 62: 1-7)
      - ., October (Box-folder 63: 1-2)
      - ., November (Folder 63: 3-5)
    - Standard Form POW Interrogation #3
      - Undated (Folder 63: 6)
      - ., 1944
        - Unnumbered (Folder 63: 7-8)
        - 1-25 (Folder 63: 9)
        - 26-45 (Box-folder 64: 1)
        - 46-66 (Folder 64: 2)
        - 67-94 (Folder 64: 3)
        - 99-110 (Folder 64: 4)
        - 111-115 (Folder 64: 5)
        - 116-130 (Folder 64: 6)
        - 131-143 (Folder 65: 1)
        - 144-160 (Folder 65: 2)
        - 161-183 (Folder 65: 3)
        - 184-206 (Folder 65: 4)
        - 207-227 (Folder 65: 5)
        - 228-247 (Folder 65: 6)
        - 248-259 (Box-folder 66: 1)
        - 261-277 (Folder 66: 2)
        - 278-307 (Folder 66: 3)
        - 308-325 (Folder 66: 4)
        - 326-347 (Folder 66: 5)
        - 348-376 (Folder 66: 6)
        - 377-394 (Folder 66: 7)
- Subject File, 1914-1949 (Boxes 67-87)
  Administrative orders, bulletins, clipping, correspondence, diary, memoranda, pamphlets, posters, printed matter, reports, radio broadcast transcripts. Arranged alphabetically by subject
  - General
    - Clippings (Folder 67: 1)
    - Notes (Folder 67: 2)
  - Allied Expeditionary Forces. Supreme Headquarters.
  - Antwerp and Rotterdam, Harbors (Folder 67: 3)
  - Austria, 1933-1945 (Folder 67: 4)
  - Czechoslovakia, 1947, Transport in (Folder 67: 5)
  - Denazification
    - General (Folder 67: 6)
    - Bürgermeisters (Box-folder 68: 1)
    - Henzler, Reinhold (Folder 68: 2)
    - Theisinger, Karl (Folder 68: 3)
  - Europe, Economic conditions in (Folder 68: 4)
  - France,., 1940-1944 (Folder 68: 5)
  - German attitude to Allies (Folder 68: 6)
  - German mass media
    - General (Folder 68: 7)
    - Books (Folder 68: 8)
    - Censorship
      - ., 1939-1940 (Folder 68: 9)
      - ., 1945 (Folder 68: 10)
    - Establishments
      - General (Folder 68: 11)
      - Verlag G.m.b.H. (Folder 68: 12)
    - Magazines and newspapers (Folder 68: 13)
    - Motion pictures (Folder 68: 14)
    - Newspapers.
      See also SUBJECT FILE/German mass media/Magazines and newspapers
      - Allgemeine Zeitung. Letters to the editor,., 1945
        - ., August (Folder 68: 15)
        - ., September (Folder 68: 16)
        - ., October (Folder 69: 1-3)
        - ., November (Folder 69: 4)
      - Deutsche allgemeine Zeitung,., 1918 (Folder 69: 5)
      - Das freie deutsche Wort,., 1917 (Folder 69: 6)
      - Frankfurter Zeitung,., 1917 (Folder 69: 7)
      - Der Führer,., 1945 (Folder 69: 8)
      - Katholisches Kirchenblatt,., 1934 (Folder 69: 9)
      - Leipziger Volkszeitung,., 1918 (Folder 69: 10)
      - Nachrichtenblatt,., 1923 (Folder 69: 11)
      - Nachrichtendienst,., 1924 (Folder 69: 12)
      - Neue Zeit,., 1947 (Folder 69: 13)
      - Neue Zeitung. Letters to editor,., 1945-1946 (Folder 69: 14)
      - Sonntags-Kurier,., 1934 (Folder 69: 15)
      - Völkischer Beobachter,., 1941 (Folder 69: 16)
      - Vorwärts,., 1923 (Folder 69: 17)
      - Die Wacht,., 1944 (Folder 69: 18)
      - Westfälische Tageszeitung,., 1945 (Folder 69: 19)
    - Radio (Folder 69: 20)
  - German national characteristics (Box-folder 70: 1-2)
  - German question (Folder 70: 3)
  - German refugees (Folder 70: 4)
  - Germany
    - General (Folder 70: 5)
    - Agriculture. (Folder 70: 6)
      See also SUBJECT FILE/Germany/ Reichsministerium f_rtschaft
    - Allied Control Authority (Folder 70: 7)
    - Allied Kommandatura, Berlin (Folder 70: 8)
    - Allied press on (Folder 70: 9)
    - Anti-Nazi underground movements in
      - Leaflets and pamphlets (Folder 70: 10)
      - Reports (Folder 70: 11)
    - Berlin district.
      See also SUBJECT FILE/Germany/ Allied Kommandatura, Berlin
      - General (Folder 70: 12)
      - Soviet zone of occupation (Folder 70: 13)
    - Bernau, Richard (Folder 70: 14)
    - Catholic youth organizations (Folder 70: 15)
    - City population (Folder 70: 16)
    - Combined Nutrition Committee (Folder 70: 17)
    - Communists in,., 1939 (Folder 70: 18)
    - Communities
      - General (Folder 70: 19)
      - General (Box-folder 71: 1-2)
      - Herzogenrath (Folder 71: 3)
    - Concentration camps in (Folder 71: 4)
    - Constitutions - Länder (Folder 71: 5)
    - Economic conditions (Folder 71: 6)
    - Evacuation of German factories by Russians (Folder 71: 7)
    - Foreign policy
      - ., 1933 (Folder 71: 8)
      - ., 1939 (Folder 71: 9)
    - Geheime Staatspolizei
      - General
        - Interrogation forms (Folder 71: 10)
        - Report on the Society of Friends (Folder 71: 11)
      - Training school (Folder 71: 12)
      - Telegraph codes (Folder 71: 13)
    - German Economic Council (Folder 71: 14)
    - Hitler, Adolf
      - Assassination attempt,., July 1944 (Folder 71: 15)
      - Birthday,., 1944 (Folder 71: 16)
    - Hospitals (Box-folder 72: 1)
    - Inter-Allied military, naval, and air control commissions. Summaries of the final report (Folder 72: 2)
    - Jews in (Folder 72: 3)
    - Justice, Administration of (Folder 72: 4)
    - Labor and laboring classes
      - General (Folder 72: 5)
      - Land labor ministries in the U.S. Zone (Folder 72: 6)
    - Ordnungspolizei (Folder 72: 7)
    - Political parties
      - General (Folder 72: 8)
      - Christlich-Demokratische Union Deutschlands (Folder 72: 9)
      - Nationalsozialistische Deutsche Arbeiterpartei.
        See also SUBJECT FILE/ Italy/Political conditions
        - Hauptarchiv (Folder 72: 10)
        - Kreisbauernführers.
          See SUBJECT FILE/ Germany/Political parties/ Nationalsozialistische Deutsche Arbeiterpartei/Landsbauernführers
        - Landsbauernführers (Folder 72: 11)
        - Local offices
          - Köln (Folder 72: 12)
          - Mannheim (Folder 72: 13)
          - Speyer (Folder 72: 14)
          - Waldshut (Folder 72: 15)
        - Policies towards
          - Birthrate (Folder 72: 16)
          - Musical establishments (Folder 72: 17)
        - Reichsverfügungsblatt (Folder 72: 18)
        - Structure (Folder 72: 19)
    - Politics
      - ., 1917 (Folder 72: 20)
      - ., 1923-1924 (Folder 72: 21)
    - Reichsministerium für Ernährung und Landwirtschaft (Box-folder 73: 1)
    - Reichsgetreide Ges. (Folder 73: 2)
    - Rural police (Folder 73: 3)
    - Thüringisches Ministerium des Innern (Folder 73: 4)
    - Wehrmacht
      - General (Folder 73: 5)
      - Deserters (Folder 73: 6)
      - Identification cards (Folder 73: 7)
      - Kriegsmarine (Folder 73: 8)
      - Luftwaffe officers as interpreters (Folder 73: 9)
      - Medical services (Folder 73: 10)
      - Versailles, Treaty of, - Evasion of military provisions, 1919 (Folder 73: 11)
      - Volkssturm (Folder 73: 12)
    - Women and children in (Folder 73: 13)
    - Youth organizations in.
      See SUBJECT FILE/Germany/ Catholic youth organizations
  - Germany After War Conference, Columbia University, New York,., April-May 1944 (Folder 73: 14)
  - Germany, East (Folder 73: 15)
  - Great Britain
    - British Broadcasting Corporation
      - Austrian section
        - General
          - Memorandum (Folder 73: 16)
          - Minutes of board meeting (Folder 73: 17)
        - Programs
          - General
            - Schedules (Folder 73: 18)
            - Stories (Folder 73: 19)
          - Austrian features (Folder 73: 20)
          - Austrian talk (Folder 73: 21)
          - Prisoners of war
            - List of POWs' relatives (Folder 73: 22)
            - Scripts
              - ., 1944
                - Handwritten (Folder 73: 23)
                - Typewritten (Folder 73: 24)
              - ., 1945 (Box 74)
                - General (Folder 74: 1)
                - Stappler, Arthur, Compiler and producer (Folder 74: 2)
      - Foreign workers (Folder 74: 3)
      - German Prisoners of War Service (Folder 74: 4)
      - Listeners' poll (Folder 74: 5)
      - Personnel. Drawings (Box-folder 75: 1)
    - Newspapers (Folder 75: 2)
    - Political Intelligence Department (Folder 75: 3)
  - Italy
    - Allied Control Commission (Folder 75: 4)
    - Allied military courts. Instructions (Folder 75: 5)
    - Allied Military Government
      - Piedmont region
        - Operational procedures. Guide for regional officers (Folder 75: 6)
        - Public Works and Utilities Division (Folder 75: 7)
      - Sicily.
        See SUBJECT FILE/United States/ Army/Counterintelligence in Sicily
    - Art objects - Conservation and restoration (Folder 75: 8)
    - Banco di Napoli (Folder 75: 9)
    - East coast - Port and terminal facilities (Folder 75: 10)
    - Economic policy
      - ., 1931-1936 (Folder 75: 11)
      - ., 1944-1945 (Box-folder 76: 1)
    - Political conditions. Report by the Nationalsozialistische Deutsche Arbeiterpartei (Folder 76: 2)
  - Japan
    - General
      - Maps (Folder 76: 3)
      - Press releases (Folder 76: 4)
    - Censorship (Folder 76: 5)
    - Economic, political, and social conditions (Folder 76: 6)
    - Education.
      See SUBJECT FILE/Japan/Moral, Psychological effect of education on
    - Industrial production (Folder 76: 7)
    - Laws and regulations (Folder 76: 8)
    - Morale, Psychological effect of education on (Folder 76: 9)
    - Political conditions.
      See SUBJECT FILE/Japan/ Economic, political, and social conditions
    - Prisoners of war. Interrogation reports (Folder 76: 10)
    - Social conditions.
    - Supreme Commander for the Allied Powers. Memoranda for Japanese government
      - 1945 (Folder 76: 11)
      - 1946 (Folder 76: 12)
      - 1948
        - January (Folder 76: 13)
        - May (Folder 76: 14)
        - October (Folder 76: 15)
        - November (Folder 76: 16)
        - December (Folder 76: 17)
      - 1949
        - January (Folder 76: 18)
        - February (Folder 76: 19)
        - March (Folder 76: 20)
        - April (Folder 76: 21)
        - May (Box-folder 77: 1)
        - June (Folder 77: 2)
        - July (Folder 77: 3)
        - August (Folder 77: 4)
        - September (Folder 77: 5)
        - October (Folder 77: 6)
        - November (Folder 77: 7)
    - United States Army requisitions, 1945 September 26 (Folder 77: 8)
  - Kriegsgeist and Geistige Kriegführung. Research project at the Hoover Institution, Stanford University (Folder 77: 9)
  - Russian national characteristics (Folder 77: 10)
  - Society of Friends.
    See SUBJECT FILE/Germany/Geheime Staatspolizei/General/Report on the Society of Friends
  - Spain - Civil War, 1936-1939 (Folder 77: 11)
  - Supreme Headquarters Allied Expeditionary Forces
    - General (Folder 77: 12)
    - G-5 Division. Information Section Library (Folder 77: 13)
    - Psychological Warfare Division
      - General (Box-folder 77: 14)
      - Radio Luxemburg Detachment
        - General
          - Correspondence (Folder 77: 15)
          - Memoranda (Folder 77: 16)
        - Foreign Workers Department.
          See also SUBJECT FILE/Supreme Headquarters Allied Expeditionary Forces/ Psychological Warfare Division/ Radio Luxemburg Detachment/Radio programs
          - General (Folder 77: 17)
          - Office equipment (Folder 77: 18)
          - Personnel (Folder 77: 19)
          - Radio programs
            - General
              - Undated (Folder 77: 20)
              - ., 1944
                - ., November (Folder 77: 21)
                - ., December (Folder 77: 22)
              - ., 1945
                - ., January (Folder 77: 23)
                - ., February (Folder 77: 24)
                - ., March (Folder 77: 25)
                - ., April (Folder 77: 26)
                - ., May (Folder 77: 27)
                - ., June (Folder 77: 28)
                - ., July (Folder 77: 29)
                - ., August (Folder 77: 30)
                - ., September (Folder 77: 31)
                - ., October (Folder 77: 32)
                - ., November (Folder 77: 33)
            - Dutch program (Folder 77: 34)
            - Music (Folder 77: 35)
            - Sunday (Folder 77: 36)
            - Sections (Box-folder 78: 1)
              - Belgian
                - Lay outs (Folder 78: 1)
                - Memoranda (Folder 78: 2)
              - Italian
                - Lay outs,., 1945
                - Memoranda (Folder 78: 5)
              - Polish (Folder 78: 6)
            - Sources of information
              - Displaced persons. Interviews
                - General (Folder 78: 7)
                - Belgian (Folder 78: 8)
                - Czech (Folder 78: 9)
                - Dutch (Folder 78: 10)
                - French (Folder 78: 11)
                - Italian (Folder 78: 12)
                - Polish (Folder 78: 13)
              - Newspapers, periodicals, etc. (Folder 78: 14)
        - German Department (Box-folder 79: 1)
        - Radio programs
          - General
            - Censored stories
              - Undated (Folder 79: 2)
              - ., 1945
                - ., February (Folder 79: 3)
                - ., March (Folder 79: 4)
                - ., April (Folder 79: 5)
                - ., May (Folder 79: 6)
                - ., June (Folder 79: 7)
                - ., July (Folder 79: 8)
                - ., August (Folder 79: 9)
                - ., September (Folder 79: 10)
                - ., October (Folder 79: 11)
            - Instructions (Folder 79: 12)
            - Scripts (Box-folder 80: 1)
          - Agricultural program (Folder 80: 2)
          - Names program
            - General (Folder 80: 3)
            - Correspondence
              - Undated (Folder 80: 4)
              - ., 1945
                - ., July (Folder 80: 5)
                - ., August (Folder 80: 6)
                - ., September (Folder 80: 7)
                - ., October (Folder 80: 8)
                - ., November (Folder 80: 9)
            - List of names (Folder 80: 10)
        - Staff message control (Folder 80: 11)
  - Switzerland. Reports (Box 81)
    - Economic policy during World War II (Folder 81: 1)
    - Neutrality of (Folder 81: 2)
    - Refugees in.
      See SUBJECT FILE/Switzerland/Work camps
    - Work camps in (Folder 81: 3)
  - Union of Soviet Socialist Republics
    - Kommunisticheskaia Partiia Sovetskogo Soiuza, XVIII Congress of the (Folder 81: 4)
    - Soviet organizations, Meeting of,., 1917? (Folder 81: 5)
  - United Nations (Folder 81: 6)
  - United States
    - Army
      - General (Folder 81: 7)
      - Counterintelligence in Sicily (Folder 81: 8)
      - European Theater of Operation.
        See also SUBJECT FILE/United States/Army/Office of Military Government for Germany
        - General (Folder 81: 9)
        - Communications (Folder 81: 10)
        - Information Control Division (Folder 81: 11)
        - Military intelligence interrogators and investigators (Folder 81: 12)
        - Military police (Folder 81: 13)
        - Motor vehicle operation procedures (Folder 81: 14)
        - Personnel
          - General (Folder 81: 15)
          - Civilian (Folder 81: 16)
        - Public relations (Folder 81: 17)
        - Relations with Allied troops (Folder 81: 18)
        - Security procedures (Folder 81: 19)
      - Office of Military Government for Germany
        - General
        - ., 1945
          - Undated
          - ., 1945
            - ., July
              - ., 7 (Folder 81: 21)
              - ., 7 (Folder 82: 1)
              - ., 23 (Folder 82: 2)
              - ., 30 (Folder 82: 3)
            - ., July-August (Folder 82: 4)
            - ., August (Folder 82: 5)
            - ., September
              - ., 5-7 (Folder 82: 6)
              - ., 16 (Folder 82: 7)
              - ., 20-26 (Folder 82: 8)
            - ., October (Folder 82: 9)
            - ., November (Folder 82: 10)
            - ., December (Folder 82: 11)
          - ., 1946
            - ., January (Folder 82: 12)
            - ., October (Folder 82: 13)
          - ., 1947 (Folder 82: 14)
        - Bremen Port Command (Folder 82: 15)
        - Conference,. Minutes, October 1945 (Folder 82: 16)
        - Information Control Service (Folder 82: 17)
        - Ministerial Collecting Center (Box-folder 83: 1)
        - Oberbayern, Regierungsbezirk (Folder 83: 2)
        - Personnel.
          See also SUBJECT FILE/ United States/Army/Office of Military Government for Germany/ Oberbayern, Regierungsbezirk; and SUBJECT FILE/United States/ Army/ Office of Military Government for Germany/Traunstein, Landkreis
          - General (Folder 83: 3)
          - Finance officers (Folder 83: 4)
        - Traunstein, Landkreis (Folder 83: 5-7)
      - Officers' Reserve Corps (Folder 83: 8)
    - Citizens in Germany (Folder 83: 9)
    - Committee on Educational Reconstruction (Folder 83: 10)
    - Economic Cooperation Administration (Folder 83: 11)
    - Economic Indicators,., January 1949 (Folder 83: 12)
    - Emigration and immigration law (Folder 83: 13)
    - German view of the (Folder 83: 14)
    - History - Bibliography (Folder 83: 15)
    - Library of Congress (Folder 83: 16)
    - Nazi view of the.
      See SUBJECT FILE/United States/German view of the
    - Office of the Chief of Counsel (Box-folder 84: 1)
    - Office of the Political Adviser (Folder 84: 2)
    - Princeton University School of Military Government (Folder 84: 3)
    - War Department (Folder 84: 4)
  - World War,., 1914-1918 (Folder 84: 5)
    Clippings, posters, printed matter regarding mainly antiwar propaganda and administration of the occupied territories in Russia by German troops
  - World War,., 1939-1945
    - General (Folder 84: 6)
    - Aerial operations, American (Folder 84: 7)
    - Atrocities
      - German reactions to. Studies (Folder 84: 8)
      - Holocaust, Jewish. Reports (in German)
        - Galicia (Folder 84: 9)
        - Warsaw (Folder 84: 10)
      - War crime trials - Nuremberg
        - Background briefing (Folder 84: 11)
        - Bulletin (Folder 84: 12)
        - Guidance notes (Folder 84: 13)
        - Speeches in defense of
          - Förtsch, Hermann, General (Folder 84: 14)
          - List, Wilhelm, Feldmarschall (Box-folder 85: 1)
          - Terberger, Hermann (Folder 85: 2)
        - Statements by defendants (Folder 85: 3)
        - Studies regarding German reactions to (Folder 85: 4)
    - British view of (Folder 85: 5)
    - Chemical warfare (Folder 85: 6)
    - Displaced persons.
      See also SUBJECT FILE/Supreme Headquarters Allied Expeditionary Forces/ Psychological Warfare Division/Radio Luxemburg Detachment/Foreign Workers Department
      - General (Folder 85: 7)
      - France (Folder 85: 8)
      - Great Britain. Political Intelligence Department, Information provided by (Box-folder 86: 1)
    - Foreign workers.
      See SUBJECT FILE/World War, 1939-1945/Displaced persons
    - Generalgouvernement (Folder 86: 2)